(Leonard:)- What?
- Sheldon's onion ring. Just put it back.
- It's one onion ring.
- Just put it back before he comes.
(Leonard:)Don't think that's where it was.
(Howard:)Okay, here he comes.
Deny, deny, deny, people. Wall of silence.
- Who touched my...?
- Penny. Penny did it.
(Sheldon:)Why would you do that?
(Penny:)I don't know. I was hungry?
What's the big deal?
(Penny:)The big deal
is that nobody touches food on my plate.
All right. I didn't know. I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm sorry,
but that is your second strike.
(Leonard:)- What?
- You have two strikes.
(Sheldon:)Three strikes and you're out.
(Sheldon:)It's a sports metaphor.
- A sports metaphor?
- Yes, baseball.
(Penny:)All right, yeah, I'll play along.
(Penny:)- What was my first strike?
- March 18th.
(Sheldon:)You violated my rule
about forwarding e-mail humor.